Perfection has a price.
Caught is a thriller, crime, mystery film directed by Maggie Kiley.
A desperate housewife discovers her husband is having an affair and kidnaps his
unsuspecting mistress, but what starts as a prank quickly spirals out of control.
Sabrina, played by Anna Camp.
Allie, played by Stefanie Scott.
Justin, played by Sam Page.
Paige, played by Amelia Rose Blaire.
Beth, played by Mary B. McCann.
Eric, played by Nick Roux.
Caught is a 2015 American psychological thriller television film directed by Maggie Kiley, written by
Marcy Holland, and starring Anna Camp, Samuel Page, Stefanie Scott and Amelia Rose Blaire.
The film explores themes of kidnapping, housewife, prank, mistress, love affair.
The tone is mind_bending and intense.